EMERSSON CHEW

www.emerssonchew.com ◆ 0220377088 ◆ emerssonchewcs@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A well rounded professional with technical skills ranging from software architecture, web development, and user experience design to business skills like social media networks for business, information systems and e-commerce for organisations, and management information systems.

SKILLS

- Requirements Gathering and Analysis
- User Experience Design
- Front-End Web Development
- Management Information Systems
- System Management and Testing

WORK HISTORY

Finance Assistant, Jan 2018 to Mar 2018

BODCO Ltd – Hamilton

Finance

- Update entries in the company's system using SAP Business ByDesign
- Liaise with other departments to prepare information for the end of financial year external audit, sales and operations plan, cost reduction plan and reports for management.

ΙT

- Provide training on SAP Business ByDesign procedures and processes
- Evaluate new IT equipment and suggest purchase options
- Configure new and reconfigure current IT equipment
- Create and maintain an IT equipment register list

Administration

• Create, review and merge company policies i.e. IT Policies, HR Policies, Communications Policies, Social Media Policies, etc.

Web Developer, Oct 2016 to June 2017

Freelance

All projects are available on www.emerssonchew.com

EDUCATION

2015 – 2017: Bachelor of Information Science: Major in Information Technology and Minor in Information Systems at **Massey University**

PROFESSIONAL MEMBERSHIPS

Associate of the IT Professionals NZ